ANTON RODICHEV

Python Developer

+381629378406 an3uryzm@gmail.com

PROFILE

Python Developer with 4+ years expertise. Experience in Project and Product manager roles.

Currently developing my side project https://scbw.gg with parsing starcraft broodwar binary files (replays) into useful information and shipping valuable analytics for players. Everything implemented on my own using Python/Django.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

❖ Founder and Developer, scbw.gg Oct 2017 — Present

Stack: Python, Django, Celery, Redis, Docker

Game database, analysis based on uploaded replays by starcraft broodwar players. Extracting data from binary files, process, and display into useful information for users.

♣ Product manager, Zoon Dec 2019 — Jun 2022

Moscow

B2B2C Product Development (automation of managing organizations' online-presence).

- plan and refine product roadmap
- · collecting and processing requirements (business, user, functional, non-functional)
- · expectations management
- product backlog prioritization and task decomposition
- · process automation
- · team training
- maintaining product documentation
- cross-team interaction (sales, dev, analytics)

Lean, Agile, Scrum

Achievements:

- 5 times lead growth (calls)
- designed architecture from scratch
- · developed MVP (some features transformed into separated successful products)
- implemented internal CRM-alike web app for transparent and scalable workflow
- designed and developed dashboards that helped our team to track progress daily and increased transparency for stakeholders
- integrations with different APIs (Google API's, +developed own APIs)

Python Developer, Zoon Feb 2017 — Dec 2019 Moscow

Implemented:

- app for managing thousands of organizations' data at external services like Google Maps or Yandex Maps (Django, Celery, Redis, PostgreSQL, UI using Django templates)
- integrations with Google API (managing business profile through Google My Business API)
- data scraping for different needs (proxy + Selenium)
- app for managing huge amount of mail accounts (collect and send via yandex api)
- API for managing vkontakte groups through VK API (python, swagger, OpenAPI)
- several telegram channels for team needs (mostly with scheduled analytical messages)
- google chrome extension for internal use

GitLab, Jira, Confluence

❖ Project/Brand manager, Universal Media		-
Full cycle driving of several brands and e-commerce projects selling high n (electronics)	nargin products in luxury segment	Nizhniy Novgorod
 department coordination (sales, marketing, dev, content creation), p forecasts, plans, reports on day/month/quarter/year basis competitor and market analysis planning supply procurement marginality and profitability control price formation web analytics 	orocess flow optimization	
Achievements:		
 Developed unified system to track business results using Power BI. N "from money to money". Reduced VoIP costs for 50% Found a ways for web landings to be more effective P&L adjustment Corrected actual and planned break-even point calculation that help 		
❖ Senior SEO specialist , Universal media		•
Increase organic traffic and sales of e-commerce projects Nizhniy Novgorod		
seo strategy, technical tasks, lead generation		
Achievements:		
 significantly decreased marketing budget by defining and implement convinced stakeholders to refuse from the services of external seo convinced 		
❖ SEO-specialist, Cyber-capital Oct 2013 − Jan 2		Oct 2013 — Jan 2014 Nizhniy Novgorod
Achieved main goal in 3 months: increased seo traffic for 15% for company's major project followed by "over-do's" in sales.		
❖ Lead SEO specialist, R-name		
Working on ~20 seo projects simultaneously (special vehicles, wedding salons, hotels, car dealers). Help to interview new people. Training junior seo specialists.		
EDUCATION		
❖ Nizhny Novgorod Aviation Technical College		
Management, Aircraft manufacturing manager		
SKILLS		
Python	Docker	
Django	Git	
SQL	Product management	
	Agile Project Management	
Celery Selenium	right i roject management	
LANGUAGES		
English C1	Russian	Native speaker